let questions = [{"numb": 1, "question": "almost kannada: durlabha, virala, saakagada", "answer": "knapp", "options": ["Abfall", "Mangel", "knapp", "Betrieb"]}, {"numb": 2, "question": "Leadership, Conduct", "answer": "Leitung", "options": ["Dreieck", "Ablauf", "Leitung", "Urteil"]}, {"numb": 3, "question": "Details ,  Kannada : dattamsha", "answer": "Angabe", "options": ["Geb\u00e4ude", "Angabe", "knapp", "Verlauf"]}, {"numb": 4, "question": "Frequently", "answer": "H\u00e4ufig", "options": ["Angabe", "Ahnung", "Geb\u00e4ude", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 5, "question": "Weather, Kannada: Havaamaana", "answer": "Gewitter", "options": ["Gewitter", "Betrieb", "knapp", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 6, "question": "Suit, Costume", "answer": "Anzug", "options": ["H\u00e4ufig", "Anzug", "Leitung", "Vorw\u00e4rts"]}, {"numb": 7, "question": "buildings", "answer": "Geb\u00e4ude", "options": ["Geb\u00e4ude", "Seitew\u00e4rts", "bedinungen", "Gabe"]}, {"numb": 8, "question": "forward", "answer": "Vorw\u00e4rts", "options": ["Vorw\u00e4rts", "Vertrag", "Angabe", "Geb\u00e4ude"]}, {"numb": 9, "question": "expired", "answer": "Ablauf", "options": ["Gewitter", "kreis", "Vierecke", "Ablauf"]}, {"numb": 10, "question": "Assumption", "answer": "Ahnung", "options": ["Betrieb", "Vertrag", "Vierecke", "Ahnung"]}, {"numb": 11, "question": "Task", "answer": "Aufgabe", "options": ["Aufgabe", "Schrifft", "Dreieck", "Abfall"]}, {"numb": 12, "question": "Talent", "answer": "Gabe", "options": ["Ahnung", "Anzug", "kreis", "Gabe"]}, {"numb": 13, "question": "term, conditon kannada: sharattugalu", "answer": "bedinungen", "options": ["Ablauf", "Ahnung", "bedinungen", "Hinweise"]}, {"numb": 14, "question": "Script", "answer": "Schrifft", "options": ["Ahnung", "Hinweise", "Vorw\u00e4rts", "Schrifft"]}, {"numb": 15, "question": "Crucial", "answer": "Wesentlich", "options": ["Gabe", "Wesentlich", "bedinungen", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 16, "question": "process", "answer": "Verlauf", "options": ["Verlauf", "Anzug", "Leitung", "Gewitter"]}, {"numb": 17, "question": "trip, Clue, Sulivu", "answer": "Hinweise", "options": ["Behalter", "Hinweise", "Mangel", "kreis"]}, {"numb": 18, "question": "Shortage, Mangelhaft(Noun)", "answer": "Mangel", "options": ["Leitung", "Aufgabe", "Mangel", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 19, "question": "Operation,", "answer": "Betrieb", "options": ["Betrieb", "Vierecke", "Ahnung", "H\u00e4ufig"]}, {"numb": 20, "question": "Sideways", "answer": "Seitew\u00e4rts", "options": ["Gabe", "Seitew\u00e4rts", "H\u00e4ufig", "Betrieb"]}, {"numb": 21, "question": "Wastage", "answer": "Abfall", "options": ["Hinweise", "Betrieb", "Gewitter", "Abfall"]}, {"numb": 22, "question": "Container", "answer": "Behalter", "options": ["Seitew\u00e4rts", "Behalter", "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Abfall"]}, {"numb": 23, "question": "Triangle", "answer": "Dreieck", "options": ["Dreieck", "Anzug", "Behalter", "Leitung"]}, {"numb": 24, "question": "Rectangular", "answer": "Vierecke", "options": ["Vierecke", "bedinungen", "Vertrag", "Hinweise"]}, {"numb": 25, "question": "Judgement", "answer": "Urteil", "options": ["Geb\u00e4ude", "Schrifft", "Betrieb", "Urteil"]}, {"numb": 26, "question": "Contract", "answer": "Vertrag", "options": ["Leitung", "Verlauf", "Vertrag", "Vorw\u00e4rts"]}, {"numb": 27, "question": "circle", "answer": "kreis", "options": ["Seitew\u00e4rts", "bedinungen", "Vorw\u00e4rts", "kreis"]}, {"numb": 28, "question": "Backward", "answer": "Ruckw\u00e4rts", "options": ["Ruckw\u00e4rts", "Hinweise", "H\u00e4ufig", "kreis"]}];